[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n ______ raining?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Is it",
            "B": "Does",
            "C": "It",
            "D": "Is"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n ______ to Milan?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Have you been",
            "B": "Have you be",
            "C": "Have you",
            "D": "You be"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n ______ to see that film that is on at the cinema next week?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Do you go",
            "B": "Is you going",
            "C": "Are you going",
            "D": "Will you go"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n ______ it was very cold, she wasn't wearing a coat.",
        "options": {
            "A": "So",
            "B": "Although",
            "C": "Because",
            "D": "But"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n ______ John this morning?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Did you see",
            "B": "You saw",
            "C": "Did you seen",
            "D": "You did see"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n ______ she's very nice, she doesn't have many friends.",
        "options": {
            "A": "Although",
            "B": "Because",
            "C": "But",
            "D": "So"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n A thermometer is a tool ______ measuring the temperature.",
        "options": {
            "A": "to",
            "B": "for",
            "C": "of",
            "D": "at"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n A: Do you like shopping? B: ______.",
        "options": {
            "A": "Yes, I am",
            "B": "Yes, I do",
            "C": "No, I do",
            "D": "No, I am"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n Bob will meet ______ at the airport.",
        "options": {
            "A": "us",
            "B": "we",
            "C": "our",
            "D": "ours"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n Can I ______ your sweater, please? It's cold and I have only a T-shirt.",
        "options": {
            "A": "borrow",
            "B": "get",
            "C": "give",
            "D": "lend"
        },
        "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D.\n Can you ______ me all right over there because you are rather a long way away?",
        "options": {
            "A": "listening",
            "B": "hearing",
            "C": "listen",
            "D": "hear"
        },
        "correct_answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Can you drive ______",
        "options": {
            "A": "more slowly",
            "B": "slowy",
            "C": "most slowly",
            "D": "slowerly"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Do you ______ clean the house every day or every week?",
        "options": {
            "A": "must",
            "B": "have",
            "C": "have to",
            "D": "must to"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Do you sell stamps? Yes, we do. How ______ do you want?",
        "options": {
            "A": "many",
            "B": "much",
            "C": "little",
            "D": "lot"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. He isn't as ______ you.",
        "options": {
            "A": "smarter as",
            "B": "smart as",
            "C": "smarter than",
            "D": "smartest"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. How many bedrooms ______ in your flat?",
        "options": {
            "A": "is there",
            "B": "are there",
            "C": "there is",
            "D": "it was"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. How many brothers and sisters______ ?",
        "options": {
            "A": "have you got",
            "B": "have you",
            "C": "you have",
            "D": "got you"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I ______ her every day and she never says hello to me.",
        "options": {
            "A": "see",
            "B": "am seeing",
            "C": "will see",
            "D": "saw"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I ______ to remember your name but I'm afraid I can't remember it.",
        "options": {
            "A": "try",
            "B": "am trying",
            "C": "trying",
            "D": "will trying"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I don't want ______ juice, thanks.",
        "options": {
            "A": "any",
            "B": "many",
            "C": "few",
            "D": "something"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I have never ______ her before.",
        "options": {
            "A": "saw",
            "B": "seeing",
            "C": "seen",
            "D": "see"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I like this apartment but the ______ is too expensive for me.",
        "options": {
            "A": "rent",
            "B": "money",
            "C": "number",
            "D": "finance"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I may ______ able to come to your party if I have the time.",
        "options": {
            "A": "be",
            "B": "being",
            "C": "being to",
            "D": "been"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I need my computer ______ send an important email",
        "options": {
            "A": "of",
            "B": "about",
            "C": "to",
            "D": "for"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I only want ______ little sugar in my tea, please.",
        "options": {
            "A": "a",
            "B": "the",
            "C": "such",
            "D": "-"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I want to go to the cinema to see a film about ______ and the French.",
        "options": {
            "A": "France",
            "B": "a France",
            "C": "the France",
            "D": "an France"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I woke up ______ there was a noise.",
        "options": {
            "A": "so",
            "B": "because",
            "C": "although",
            "D": "but"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I'm looking at the photograph ______ you sent me with your letter.",
        "options": {
            "A": "which",
            "B": "who",
            "C": "whom",
            "D": "whose"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. I'm going to a concert tonight. ______ you like to come?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Would",
            "B": "Are",
            "C": "Do",
            "D": "Is"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. It is ______ book that I have ever read.",
        "options": {
            "A": "funniest",
            "B": "a funniest",
            "C": "the funniest",
            "D": "the most funniest"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. My current job is ______ more stressful than my last job.",
        "options": {
            "A": "much",
            "B": "many",
            "C": "very",
            "D": "lot"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. My sister's studying the law ______ university.",
        "options": {
            "A": "at",
            "B": "for",
            "C": "inside",
            "D": "of"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Now will you please ______ me and pay attention to what I'm saying because it's very important.",
        "options": {
            "A": "hear",
            "B": "listen to",
            "C": "hearing",
            "D": "listening to"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Paula ______ loves working with children.",
        "options": {
            "A": "really",
            "B": "more",
            "C": "very",
            "D": "much"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Picasso and Monet ______ famous painters.",
        "options": {
            "A": "was",
            "B": "were",
            "C": "is",
            "D": "are"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. She's going to university ______ her studies.",
        "options": {
            "A": "for continuing",
            "B": "to continue",
            "C": "to continuing",
            "D": "continue"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. The brothers will ______ school both together at the end of this year.",
        "options": {
            "A": "end",
            "B": "ending",
            "C": "finish",
            "D": "finishes"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. The bus didn't stop in Lyon. It only ______ in Paris.",
        "options": {
            "A": "didn't stop",
            "B": "stopped",
            "C": "stop",
            "D": "stopping"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. The grass, ______ I cut every week, seems to grow very quickly.",
        "options": {
            "A": "who",
            "B": "who's",
            "C": "which",
            "D": "that"
        },
        "correct_answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. There was nothing on TV, ______ I went to bed.",
        "options": {
            "A": "so",
            "B": "but",
            "C": "because",
            "D": "although"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. This is going to be ______ show you have ever seen",
        "options": {
            "A": "the biggest",
            "B": "the bigger",
            "C": "the bigger",
            "D": "bigger"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. We couldn't find a taxi, ______ we walked home.",
        "options": {
            "A": "so",
            "B": "but",
            "C": "because",
            "D": "although"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. What is ______ option in the menu?",
        "options": {
            "A": "healthier",
            "B": "the healthiest",
            "C": "most healthy",
            "D": "health"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. What time ______ call you tomorrow?",
        "options": {
            "A": "should I",
            "B": "I should",
            "C": "do I should",
            "D": "should do I"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. What's ______ river in the world?",
        "options": {
            "A": "the longest",
            "B": "longer",
            "C": "long",
            "D": "more long"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. When will you ______ come and see us in our new house?",
        "options": {
            "A": "can",
            "B": "be able to",
            "C": "must",
            "D": "being able"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. When ______ a decision?",
        "options": {
            "A": "will she make",
            "B": "she will make",
            "C": "make she",
            "D": "she making"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Where ______ for dinner last night?",
        "options": {
            "A": "did you went",
            "B": "did you go",
            "C": "you went",
            "D": "you are"
        },
        "correct_answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Which of these is a noun?",
        "options": {
            "A": "thing",
            "B": "think",
            "C": "that",
            "D": "there"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Which of these is an adjective? It is ______",
        "options": {
            "A": "hard",
            "B": "hardly",
            "C": "harden",
            "D": "hardship"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "Choose the correct answer: A, B, C or D. Who ______ to the party?",
        "options": {
            "A": "did Sandra invite",
            "B": "Sandra did invite",
            "C": "inviting Sandra",
            "D": "Sandra don't invite"
        },
        "correct_answer": "A"
    }
]